准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
泡泡店
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
多美好的一天啊
What a wonderful day
阳光明媚  波光粼粼
The sun is out, the water is shimmering
贝壳快乐地叫着
scallops are chirping
好安静
So peaceful
拜托能不能小点声
Can we lower the volume, please
这么吵害我干不了正事
I can't work with all that racket going on
好的  章鱼哥
Sure thing, Squidward
这才对
Right
好的
Okay
现在来听听章鱼哥竖笛的美妙音乐吧
And now for some soothing sounds
from Squidward's clarinet
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you
我不是
I thought I--
泡泡
章鱼哥  要不要来吹泡泡
Hey, Squidward, want to blow some bubbles?
只要两毛五
Only 25 cents
太对了
Right
搞得好像我会浪费时间吹泡泡一样
like I would spend a moment of my time blowing bubbles
行行好
Oh, please
我是说  谁会特别花钱去吹泡泡
I mean, who in the world would pay to blow bubbles?
早安
Good morning
天啊
Oh, boy
你也早  先生
Good morning to you, sir
要来吹泡泡吗
Would you care to blow a bubble?
要多少钱
How much is it?
只要两毛五
Only a quarter
价格挺合理
Sounds reasonable
我得去借两毛五
I'm going to need to borrow a quarter
没问题  派大星
Sure thing, Patrick
两毛五
One quarter
谢谢
Thank you
生意火起来了
Business is booming
我怎么会跟这么废的邻居住在一起
How did I ever get surrounded by such loser neighbors?
泡泡
一根泡泡棒
One bubble wand
蘸完泡泡水可以吹了
dipped and ready to go
教程
愿意参与教程吗
Could I interest you in some lessons?
只要两毛五
Only 25 cents
那就好
Very well, then
海绵宝宝  我能再借两毛五吗
Hey, sponge, can I borrow another quarter?
谢了
Thanks
派大星  全都在于技巧
Okay, Patrick, it's all in the technique
首先这样
First go like this
转个圈
spin around
停
stop
甩头回神三遍
Double-take three times
一  二  三
one, two, three
然后骨盆俯冲
then pelvic thrust
用右脚站住
Stop on your right foot
记住这一点
Don't forget it
现在开始转个大圈
Now it's time to bring it around town
转个大圈
Bring it around town
然后你这样
Then you do this
再这样
then this
这样
and this
然后那样
then that
这样那样
and this and that
然后
and then--
现在用两只手
And now with two hands
是头长颈鹿
It's a giraffe
打烊
不好意思先生  我们打烊了
Excuse me, sir, but we are close
别说有的没的
Don't give me any of that
你们两个吹个泡泡
How could you two possibly make
怎么会那么吵
all this noise just blowing bubbles?
泡泡
我们不仅仅是在吹泡泡
We're not just blowing bubbles
我们是在创造泡泡艺术
we're making bubble art
看好了
Watch carefully
首先这样
First go like this
转个圈
spin around
停
stop
甩头回神三遍
Double-take three times
一  二  三
one, two, three
然后骨盆俯冲
then pelvic thrust
用右脚站住
Stop on your right foot
记住这一点
Don't forget it
现在开始转个大圈
Now it's time to bring it around town
转个大圈
Bring it around town
然后你这样
Then you do this
再这样
then this
这样
and this
然后那样
then that
这样那样
and this and that
然后
and then--
那不是艺术
That's not art
只是在烦人
That's just annoying
吹泡泡
Blowing bubbles
我听过最烂的主意
That's the lamest idea I have ever heard
你们应该为自己感到羞耻
You should be ashamed of yourself
泡泡
Bubbles--
艺术
art
泡泡
Bubbles
可笑
Ridiculous
一共两毛五  先生
That'll be 25 cents, sir
泡泡
什么
What?
谁会花两毛五去吹泡泡
Who would pay 25 cents to blow bubbles?
我们也会提供初学者教程
We also offer lessons for beginners
教程
初学者
Beginners?
还有什么事情会比吹个破泡泡要简单
What could be more simple
than blowing a stupid bubble?
两毛五给你
Here's your 25 cents
学着点
Watch and learn
等等
Wait
再来一次
One more time
来  等着
Here, wait
单纯在热身罢了
Just a mere warm-up
章鱼哥  记住技巧
Hey, Squidward, remember the technique
章鱼哥  技巧
Squidward, technique
你要这样再这样  退回去
You do this and this, step back
技巧  章鱼哥
Technique, Squidward
这样转个圈
Spin around like this
在这
Over here
一  二
one, two
对  三
yeah, three--
骨盆  呜
The pelvic whoo
记得要  呜
Don't forget the whoo
章鱼哥
Squidward--
听海绵宝宝的
Listen to sponge
技巧
Technique
技
Tech--
你没用到技巧
You're not doing the technique
技巧
Technique
首先我要这样
First I do this
转个圈  停
spin around, stop
甩头回神三遍
Double-take three times
然后开始
and here we go
骨盆俯冲
pelvic thrust
用右脚站住
Stop on your right foot
记住这一点
Don't forget it
再转个大圈
Then bring it around town
然后再做点这样
and a little of this
做点那样
a little of that
做点这样
a little of this
这样
this
那样
that
然后
then--
好行  章鱼哥
All right, Squid
泡泡吹得不错
That was so good
章鱼哥是第一名
Squid is number one
我成功吹出来了对吧
I really did it, didn't I?
没错  你们就是吹不出那样的泡泡
Yeah, you guys didn't blow anything like that
吹不出
Nope
这样的泡泡才像样
Now, that's a bubble
你说的  章鱼哥
You said it, Squidward
看吧  都是因为技巧
See, it is all in the technique
对  技巧
Yeah, technique
技巧
Technique?
海绵宝宝  不会你以为我吹出那个
SpongeBob, you don't think I created that--
美丽艺术品都是靠你帮忙才成的是吧
beautiful work of art with your help
拜托  都是因为我的基因强大
Come on, it's in my genes
章鱼哥有基因
Squid's got genes
谢谢
Thank you
章鱼哥
Squidward
我好酷
I rock
章鱼哥
Squidward
章鱼章鱼  章鱼哥
Squid, squid, Squidward
章鱼哥
Squidward
我的朋友们好  你们看到的是
Hello, my friends, you are looking at a--
章鱼哥
Squidward
天才
Genius
撕裂的裤子
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
欢迎来到酷乐湖
啊  酷乐湖
Ah, Goo Lagoon
对于你和我都是个臭泥坑
a stinky mud puddle to you and me
但对于裤头村的居民就是个美妙的
but to the inhabitants of Bikini Bottom a wonderful
臭泥坑
stinky mud puddle
多棒的一天
What a great day
珊迪你看
Hey, Sandy, look
我是珊迪
I'm Sandy
沙 子
珊迪  我是谁啊
Hey, Sandy, who am I?
喂  海绵宝宝
Hello, SpongeBob
能不能小点声
could you keep it down?
我很想无聊一阵子
I'm trying to be boring
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
谁点了20份辣香肠沙子披萨
Did anyone order 20 pepperoni and sand pizzas?
嗨  珊迪
Hey, Sandy
嗨  海绵宝宝
Hey, SpongeBob
嗨  拉里
Hey, Larry
你们要去举重吗
You guys want to go lift some weights?
好啊
Sure
快来吧  海绵宝宝
Come on, SpongeBob
来了
Coming
试试吧  珊迪
Give it a try, Sandy
好样的  珊迪
Good job, Sandy
今天就差不多到此为止了
Well, that's about enough for today
要不再加重一点怎么样
How about a little more weight?
看好了
Observe
好了
All right
大家都退后
Stand back, everyone
瞧好了
Y'all watch this
好样的  拉里
Way to go, Larry
能借几个这个吗
Could I borrow a couple of these?
现在  再加上两个
And now, with the addition of two
数一下
count them
两个  棉花糖
two, marshmallows
太好笑了
That was too funny
你可笑死我了
You are hilarious
他是不是你见过最好笑的海绵
Ain't he the funniest little sponge you ever saw?
有谁要来打排球
Anybody up for some volleyball?
拉里
我来接
I got it
过来了
Incoming
我应该又撕破裤子了
I guess I ripped my pants again
老兄  你又笑破我肚皮了
Once again, dude, you have split my sides
珊迪
Hey, Sandy
把飞盘扔给我怎么样
How about throwing it to me?
好的  飞盘来了
Okay, here it comes
我急需人来搭把手
I could use a hand here
你没事吧  海绵宝宝
You okay, SpongeBob?
没事  只是我弄破了裤子
I guess so, except I ripped my pants
你还是好好笑  老兄
You still got it, dude
冰淇淋
需要什么服务
May I help you?
给我来份香蕉船
I'll take a banana split
撕破
这个我们没有
We don't have that
没事
That's okay
我已经弄破裤子了  听懂没
I already split my pants, get it?
还要点什么吗
Anything else?
那就  漩涡冰淇淋
how about, ripple?
撕 裂
不用了  已经有一份了
No, thanks, already got one
零食吧
你吃的是汉堡吗
Is that a burger you're eating?
没错  是汉堡
Why, yes, it is
知道汉堡要配什么才好吗
You know what would go good with that?
不知道  是什么
No, what?
撕裂的裤子
Ripped pants
加冰淇淋的破裤子
Ripped pants a la mode
快递
Delivery
你刚订购了20箱破裤子吗
Did you order 20 cases of ripped pants?
酷乐湖正在进行冲浪活动
Surf's up in the Goo Lagoon
拉里过来了  在做招牌后靠动作
And here comes Larry, doing his trademark lay-back
珊迪过来了
There goes Sandy
垂着十个  手指吧
hanging ten, fingers, that is
海绵宝宝过来了
There goes SpongeBob
又撕破了裤子
Ripping his pants again
救生员
看啊
Hey, look
一个纸盒子被冲上海滩来了
A cardboard box washed up on the beach
见鬼了这是
Holy fish paste
那是个人
It's a guy
为什么
Why?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
靠过来
Come closer
我需要
I need--
你需要什么
What do you need?
裁缝
A tailor
因为我撕破了我的裤子
Because I ripped my pants
这种玩笑开得一点不是时候
That kind of stuff is uncalled for
什么鬼玩意
What is that?
一点都不好笑  海绵宝宝
That wasn't funny, SpongeBob
你害我担心死了
Y'all had me worried sick
老兄
Dude
快啊  海绵宝宝
Come on, SpongeBob
要失去他们了
you're losing them
快想
Think
你观众还在等着呢
Your public's waiting
我想想
Let's see
举重  大笑
Lifting weights, big laugh
飞盘砸中脸  笑翻
Frisbee in face, kills
冲浪  笑死
Surfing, knocks them dead
假装溺水
Pretending to drown
不行
no
快想啊
Come on, think
有了
I got it
大家好
Hey, everybody
没有破裤子
Not ripped pants
裤子已经被扒下来了
pants ripped off
有谁来报个警
Someone call the police
有个在逃裤子贼
There's a pants thief on the loose
不会吧
Oh, no
大家都走了  连珊迪也是
Everybody's gone, even Sandy
她宁愿跟拉里在一块
She'd rather hang out with Larry
不行
Oh, no
不
No
我们搞砸了  裤子
We blew it, pants
谁跟你算是  我们
Who do you mean, we?
我根本没必要卖傻
I didn't have to be a fool
来引起珊迪的注意
to get Sandy's attention
我是海滩最大的失败者吗
Am I the biggest loser on the beach?
不  我才是
No, I am
我忘记涂防晒霜了
I forgot to put on sunscreen
不  我才是
No, I am
我面包上沾上了沙子
I got sand in my buns
不  我才是海滩最大的失败者
No, I'm the biggest loser on the beach
他们把我埋进沙子里  还把我忘了
They buried me in the sand and forgot me
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我失去了我的好朋友
I lost my best friend
怎么会
How?
当我撕裂了
When I ripped
我的裤子
My pants
我以为所有人都会喜欢我
I thought that I had everybody on my side
但我搞砸了一切
But I went and blew it all sky-high
现在她连看都不会看我一眼
And now she won't even spare a passing glance
全都是因为我
All just because I
弄破裤子
Ripped my pants
拉里过来  让海绵宝宝显得渺小
When big Larry came round just to put him down
于是海绵宝宝成了小丑
SpongeBob turned into a clown
女生们都不愿共舞
And no girl ever wants to dance
同一个破裤子的傻瓜一起
With a fool who went and ripped his pants
我知道不该闷闷不乐
I know I shouldn't mope around
也不该埋怨
I shouldn't curse
但我心中的痛愈发严重
But the pain feels so much worse
因为没人理  让一切变乏味
'Cause winding up with no one is a lot less fun
程度大于晒伤
Than a burn from the sun
还有面包沾沙
Or sand in your buns
现在我学到了难忘的教训
Now I learned a lesson I won't soon forget
现在听好  不然就会后悔
So listen and you won't regret
对自己真诚
Be true to yourself
不要错过机会
Don't miss your chance
你就不会变成
And you won't end up
破裤子的那个傻瓜
Like the fool who ripped his pants
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
珊迪
Sandy
你的歌唱得太对了
Your song is true
要想成为朋友  就只要做好自己
If y'all want to be my friend just be yourself
海绵宝宝  说得太对了
SpongeBob, that was so righteous
你愿意在我裤子上签名吗
Would you sign my pants?
可以  兄弟
Absolutely, buddy